<?xml version="1.0"?>
<contentList xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <content contentuid="h3c79d0edg5dfcg0a3cgb5ebg35c5c14223bd" version="1">Alchemist</content>
  <content contentuid="hbab3fe76ge30ag0c5fgbc66g6156ad3c399d" version="1">Infused Reagent</content>
  <content contentuid="h3cb4b477g8a7ag0fd9g7e0fg395fa82e461f" version="1">Versatile Vial</content>
  <content contentuid="h42a0b6f1gf01egbaa6g115agc227faef04d9" version="3">Hide Apron</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c201420g888cg9198g8d5dgbfc22ac3816a" version="3">A thick apron draped over a leather doublet, to protect from the worst of laboratory accidents.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd1beb9ag6e6bgef3fgfdbcg17ae9db51add" version="1">Quick Vial</content>
  <content contentuid="hddf3710bga553g5bcagc44fg787eed052034" version="1">Your versatile vials contain volatile chemicals that can be used offensively in a pinch.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2f902c42g38c9gdfe3gdf5agee86a7cd49d4" version="1">AdvancedAlchemy</content>
  <content contentuid="heed6a99eg1179g9d8dg5ed0gcc5f5b932e37" version="3">Quick Alchemy</content>
  <content contentuid="h65280855g19c9g13aeg9e9bgcb1c18d85f4b" version="1">Infused</content>
  <content contentuid="h39e39d81g0affgc092gbfe8ga8ba8b6c81f3" version="1">An alchemical item with the infused trait has a limited time before it becomes inert. Any non-permanent effects from your infused alchemical items, with the exception of afflictions such as slow-acting poisons, end when you make your daily preparations again. </content>
  <content contentuid="hd4cc6f6fg1448g7cb3g55a1gebbcf5be22a4" version="1">Grease Bottle</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e4b90cdg2a74g9685g3bd7g6ec3c68a5083" version="1">Potion of Healing</content>
  <content contentuid="hd7e57309g85c2gc851g1f5egb6b7e6e6d4c4" version="1">Potion of Healing</content>
  <content contentuid="hf01c7e53ge34eg2e84g743fg760853ba0fe1" version="1">Alchemical Formulas</content>
  <content contentuid="ha9daa1a0g2b23g570ag78c8g9b1e6dbb215d" version="1">An alchemist keeps meticulous formulas for every item they can create. Each time you gain a level, you can add the formulas for two common alchemical items to your formula book.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb139a570g10f7g3f8bg5681gc3cdc6a24c8b" version="1">Versatile Vials</content>
  <content contentuid="hefbbb426gcb7dg4ff3g1c5bg0cf754759818" version="2">Acid Bottle</content>
  <content contentuid="h86a01fefg4645gd9a4gfd3eg0006ab9929b3" version="2">Alchemist's Fire (BG3)</content>
  <content contentuid="h88ab421bg8b81g0f63g6c06g850aad47def5" version="1">Amulet Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h593c4df3g7aa4ged2cg6aefg5c2b7764d557" version="1">The protective aspects of your amulet can shield you and your allies from harm. You gain the Amulet's Abeyance reaction.&lt;br&gt;Reaction&lt;br&gt;Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability would damage you or an ally within 15 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;You forcefully present your amulet to turn away harm. You or a target ally within 15 feet gain resistance to all damage against the triggering damage. The resistance is equal to 2 + your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2e54f499g0497g3239g8478g7561974297d6" version="1">Bell Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h7dcbb14fgecfeg40eage48cg8f6d28ae8107" version="1">You can use your bell implement to create three different kinds of music, each of which weakens a foe in a different way. You gain the Ring Bell activity.&lt;br&gt;Reaction&lt;br&gt;Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability makes a Strike or Casts a Spell that would affect you or one of your allies.&lt;br&gt;Requirements You are holding your bell implement, and the triggering creature is within 30 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;Your implement sings out abruptly, disrupting your foe. The piece played depends on whether the trigger was a Strike or Spell, and it applies to the triggering Strike or Spell, except where noted otherwise.&lt;br&gt;Distracting Cacophony The trigger is a spell. You create a musical crash of sonic energy that assails the target and breaks its concentration. The target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become stupefied 1 until the end of your next turn (stupefied 2 on a critical failure). The target doesn't have to attempt a flat check to avoid losing the triggering spell, but the discordant ring does lower the spell attack roll or spell DC of the triggering spell from stupefied.&lt;br&gt;Disrupting Harmony The trigger is a Strike. You create a strangely discordant harmony that sinks into your foe's mind and throws its movements off. The target must succeed at a Will save against your class DC or become your choice of enfeebled 1 or clumsy 1 until the end of your next turn (enfeebled 2 or clumsy 2 on a critical failure).</content>
  <content contentuid="h7c5bd35dg88c1g727eg9443ga3899e85e3fc" version="1">Chalice Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="ha3fd7d80g3d5cgf01eg12f1ge85b0ff1bf8e" version="1">While holding your chalice, you can drink from it or feed its liquid to an ally to improve their health. You gain the Drink from the Chalice action.&lt;br&gt;1 Action&lt;br&gt;Frequency once per round&lt;br&gt;You drink from the liquid that slowly collects in your chalice or administer it to an adjacent ally. The drinker chooses whether to take a small sip or to drain the contents.&lt;br&gt;Sip A sip grants the drinker an amount of temporary Hit Points equal to 2 + half your level that last until the end of your next turn.&lt;br&gt;Drain (healing, positive) Drinking deep instead heals the drinker 3 Hit Points for each level you have. After the chalice is drained, it's left with only its slowly collecting dregs; the chalice can't be drained again, though it can still be sipped from. If 10 minutes pass without anyone drinking from the chalice, it refills itself and can be drained again. If the drinker has negative healing, it can still heal in this way, and the effect has the negative trait instead of healing and positive.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd80047ceg793bg34edg329eg3352fe0e5e12" version="1">Lantern Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h07605eddg378dg4339g1128g5c0123cc33b1" version="1">While you hold your lantern, its burning light leaves secrets no place to hide. You can light or extinguish your lantern as a free action once each turn with nothing but a thought, which has the concentrate trait. The lantern shines bright light out to 20 feet and dim light out 20 feet further; this has the evocation, light, and magical traits (the counteract level against magical darkness is equal to half your level rounded up).&lt;br&gt;The lantern's magical light attempts to reveal the unseen. You and your allies in the lantern's area of bright light gain a +1 status bonus to visual Perception checks to notice anything that is also within the bright light</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5dfe865gcb7eg397fg777bg785a4e3d1cf8" version="1">Mirror Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h7140187agf431g523fge2f0gf1fd32fc1d68" version="1">You learn how to use your mirror to project another version of yourself whose realness is a matter of perspective. You gain the Mirror's Reflection action.&lt;br&gt;1 Action&lt;br&gt;You reflect an illusory image of yourself into another unoccupied space within 15 feet that you can see. You are treated as being in both spaces until the start of your next turn. For example, you can attack, Seek, and provide flanking—even with yourself. You occupy both spaces.&lt;br&gt;Some events force you to determine which image is the real you, and then end the effect and cause your mirror self to disappear; this happens automatically at the start of your next turn. It also happens if you choose to move out of your space. Other benefits of this implement add more events that can end the reflection. The effect also ends when you fall unconscious, at which point you decide which version is truly you.</content>
  <content contentuid="h29a8985bg396cg3f90g849dg8324c42a2b95" version="1">Regalia Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h429aae9fgb71eg4791g62d0g5f0e83f85958" version="1">While you hold your regalia, you gain an air of authority and bolster the courage of allies who believe in you. Your regalia aids you when you attempt to convince others. You gain a +1 circumstance bonus to Deception, Diplomacy, and Intimidation checks.&lt;br&gt;When you are holding your regalia, you gain an inspiring aura that stokes the courage of you and all allies in a 15-foot emanation who can see you, granting them a +1 status bonus to saving throws against fear. At the end of your turn, at the same time you would reduce your frightened value by 1, you reduce the frightened value of all allies within your inspiring aura by 1. Your aura has the emotion, mental, and visual traits.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0962f74g9c72g6b52g0c6fg58353ee0ad33" version="1">Tome Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="h6f7e3a02gf7d0gea5cgb476g48f2ad099157" version="1">You are trained in two additional skills. You gain an additional skill increase at level 3 and 5.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf080ff16gecc6gcb1ag3511g10c69104740d" version="2">Wand Initiate (Fire)</content>
  <content contentuid="h13eb29a4gebe9gbb17g7c86g12dc0af0b470" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb3103de6gf1c2g1151gf3fbgd3ab6cf4c38a" version="1">Weapon Initiate</content>
  <content contentuid="hb8f50018g080cg8d05g2a05g3aaa92faa79c" version="1">Your weapon trembles slightly in your hand, seeking out your foe's weakness to it and interrupting their actions. You gain the Attack of Opportunity reaction.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3520d26egb29fg646bgc6b0gf179fc5a7e8c" version="1">Amulet Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h1db061f4gadb4g61d3g3a89gd41148e273e2" version="1">Your amulet offers continued protection. When you use Amulet's Abeyance, you or your ally chooses one type of damage dealt by the triggering attack and gains resistance 5 against that damage type until the start of your next turn. At 15th level, this lingering resistance increases from 5 to 10.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb01de7eg3a4cgfd2bg9fc1g11b2eb84fa5d" version="1">Bell Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="hc29b0c6fgbaeeg7de1g4221g4476a9a600f2" version="1">Your bell resonates powerfully, causing the effect to last longer. The conditions from Ring Bell last 3 rounds instead of 1 round.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e16c3a9ge236g691dga5c1gc1c7921e9366" version="1">Chalice Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h1038ab67g5159gb55ag5155g010c812fbf1c" version="1">The life essence shed from blood empowers your chalice. If you or an ally within 30 feet takes piercing or slashing damage from a foe's critical hit or takes persistent bleed damage, Drinking from the Chalice before the end of your next turn grants that injured creature greater restoration to make up for its lost vitality. On a sip, the temporary Hit Points granted to the creature increase to 2 + your Charisma modifier + your level. When drained, the chalice heals the creature 5 Hit Points for each level you have.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3aef4bfbg0b0fge11bg462bg6ed9926d8e7a" version="1">Lantern Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h4288af42g92f8g536cg1e93g29ddab2abb62" version="1">In addition to the initiate benefits, when you hold your lantern, its light reveals the invisible and the ethereal. The bright light increases to 30 feet, with dim light out 30 feet further. While you're holding your lantern, invisible and ethereal creatures within the bright light become visible as rippling distortions, though they're still concealed. This doesn't give you any special ability to affect a creature on the Ethereal Plane, but it ensures you're aware of the creatures' presence.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0a74d471g4dd2g1393gdc34gea5421d27d3f" version="1">Mirror Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb509b4ag1aa8gb599gaed5g8f4291e72949" version="1">Your mirror self shatters into punishing shards when damaged. While Mirror's Reflection is in effect, when an enemy adjacent to one of your spaces damages you, that version of you explodes into mirror shards. This ends Mirror's Reflection (establishing the remaining version of you as the real one) and deals slashing damage to all creatures in a 5-foot emanation around where your mirror self was. The damage is equal to 2 + half your level or the damage of the triggering attack, whichever is lower. You're immune to this damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9b41c3d5g7a5age7dbg48ceg32f0cc912db8" version="1">Regalia Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="hf80291e1gb313gb2d4g01e3g3d171d914033" version="1">Your regalia's power increases, and so do the abilities it grants. The circumstance bonus you gain to Deception, Diplomacy, and Intimidation increases to +2&lt;br&gt;The courage your aura instills grows stronger. The +1 status bonus now applies to all saving throws against mental effects, rather than only against fear, and you and allies in your aura gain a +2 status bonus to damage rolls. At 11th level, this increases to a +3 status bonus to damage rolls, and at 17th level, this increases to a +4 status bonus to damage rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3e540c75g488fgd2c1g49e9gc580ba9f6e74" version="1">Tome Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5dd6ce7ga693g1578g505cgc1dd4e31e073" version="1">In addition to the initiate benefits, your tome inscribes insights into creatures that you can use to strike them down. While holding your tome, at the start of your turn each round, attempt a check to Recall Knowledge about a creature of your choice that you're observing. If this check succeeds, you gain a +1 circumstance bonus to your next attack roll against that creature before the start of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5673120bg062fgcce5g2ae8g60ac9fd7af0b" version="1">Wand Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h013df7e6gaa66gc186g2dbagfe3e3f064788" version="1">You gain versatility and additional benefits when you fire your wand. The range of Fling Magic increases to 120 feet. Choose a second damage type from the list; whenever you Fling Magic, you can select between either of the two damage types you have chosen. Fling Magic has an additional effect if the target fails its save and takes damage, depending on the type.&lt;br&gt;Cold: The target becomes chilled, taking a –10-foot status penalty to its Speeds for 1 round.&lt;br&gt;Electricity: The target is shocked, becoming flat-footed until the end of your next turn.&lt;br&gt;Fire: The target catches flame, taking 1d10 persistent fire damage (or 2d10 on a critical failure). If you have the wand paragon benefit, this increases to 2d10 persistent fire damage (or 4d10 on a critical failure).</content>
  <content contentuid="h2835ecbbg6c4ag4813g6e69g96b4131d3636" version="1">Weapon Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h0defc74cgf372g901ag3a6fg791eac0effab" version="1">When your implement lashes out at your foe, even a close miss brings the weapon close enough to do harm. When you use Implement's Interruption and fail (but don't critically fail) the Strike, you deal 1 damage of the weapon's normal type, possibly applying any bonus damage due to the target's weakness.</content>
  <content contentuid="h618c5809g150bg1e04gf1f0g1ab3aa5fff8a" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Amulet)</content>
  <content contentuid="hd96118bcgb6fega3c5g3af5geb9224a1c0b2" version="1">Your amulet repels the creature's attempts to harm you. You gain a +2 status bonus to AC and saves against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbadc67f6ga101g7504g40b8ge35d0a2d97b7" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Bell)</content>
  <content contentuid="h3f9e82efg62ecgb5c7gb51fg721a18688ac9" version="2">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="h2845aa39g3d6cg0e25gbfc2gf306031d49e3" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Chalice)</content>
  <content contentuid="h68f3be88g85aeg1ae9g6eabgca8cd2b54562" version="1">Your reinforced chalice can collect a creature's life force to become empowered. If you succeed at a Strike against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you increase the effect if someone Drinks from the Chalice before the end of that turn. Add an additional half your level to the temporary HP if the drinker sips, or add your level to the HP regained if the drinker drains the chalice. This effect isn't cumulative if you hit with more than one Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf6c8ed5cgfb94gf62eg9f4bg4637d98fa23e" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Lantern)</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ee1d37dgdaf5g564dga881g79d6fbe6a076" version="2">Your lantern's light flares and burns bright, leaving no shadows in which secrets and enemies can hide. When you Strike the target of your Exploit, it loses any invisibility or blur effect.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6229f5e2g6b39ge76bgb8f3g9a43cc4aa419" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Mirror)</content>
  <content contentuid="h7507c882g1498gb5b7g970dgef4eb08c8b96" version="1">Reinforcing your mirror lets it play tricks on your enemy's senses as it bends light this way or that. You become concealed to the target of your Exploit Vulnerability as your mirror warps its perceptions. As normal for concealment where your overall location is still obvious, you can't use this concealment to Hide or Sneak.</content>
  <content contentuid="haa709951g1815g8bcag2feag8d1bf28783a2" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Regalia)</content>
  <content contentuid="h1bdfdf00gfa00g1340gee3bgf45789049271" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, choose an ally that you can see. That ally gains a +1 circumstance bonus to its attack rolls against the creature until the beginning of your next turn. If the attack roll was a critical hit, the circumstance bonus increases to +2.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6d9c3a35geef1gd866g9a10gc452db2e4485" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Tome)</content>
  <content contentuid="h11ca9522g6c6dgfb05g32f6gceb1c105eee1" version="1">Your tome's power not only reads a creature's present but even records its future actions. When you use Intensify Vulnerability, roll a d20 and set the result aside. At any time until the start of your next turn, you can use the d20 result you set aside for an attack roll to Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, instead of rolling a new d20; this is a fortune effect.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8528da86g0ac0g8aa8ge6ffg43e3788d58ac" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Wand)</content>
  <content contentuid="h01219aa1gb83dg9628g6e30g0cbf7d079482" version="1">Your empowered wand surges with ever-more-powerful magic. When you Fling Magic to damage the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you deal additional damage to the creature equal to 1 + the number of damage dice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb8dbfe23g70d5gcff6gaac1g7136b85e2868" version="1">Intensify Vulnerability (Weapon)</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c9e784dg51c9g3a62g48c2g882d8a78aacc" version="1">Your weapon is drawn to your enemy's vital spots, almost of its own accord. You gain a +2 status bonus to attack rolls against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="h71d606f4g89f5g19e9g76cag6534ff62eeb4" version="1">Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="hfe7512e8g0687g0cc1ga3a7gc0b0be80822d" version="1">Amulets are items carried for good luck and protection. Your amulet might be a magical diagram, a religious symbol, a preserved body part such as a rabbit's foot, or a lucky coin. Amulet implements are associated with the harrow suit of shields and the astrological signs of the bridge and the ogre.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4ba7d30cgab75gc188g8b95g202987364b5a" version="1">Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="ha6c50cd4g82e0gcf60g683agadcb9c618505" version="1">Bells symbolize the power that sounds and emotions hold over others, soothing with one tone and startling with another. Bells, drums, finger cymbals, and other percussion instruments are most typical, but these implements can be any type of portable musical instrument that is played with one hand. Bell implements are associated with the astrological signs of the daughter and the blossom.</content>
  <content contentuid="hefa4ffb6g0ea5g465ag3bcfgda737d67011e" version="1">Chalice</content>
  <content contentuid="hf1ae0f6fg289eg6520g6e1ag7c5965f8e3a1" version="1">Chalice implements are vessels that fill with liquid, associating them with healing, nourishment, and life. Your chalice might be a traditional cup or goblet, but it could also be a small amphora, a polished gourd, or even a hollowed-out skull. Chalice implements are associated with the astrological signs of the mother and the newlyweds, as well as the sea dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h192bd302g612ega04bg4541g3bba0576c92f" version="1">Lantern</content>
  <content contentuid="h2250ef7cgd86dgcb57g6168g97eab744149d" version="1">Lantern implements shine the light of revelation to part shadows and expose truth. You might use a common glass lantern, torch, paper lantern, or other similar light source. Lantern implements are associated with the harrow suit of stars and the astrological signs of the lantern bearer and the archer.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc2816a95gc94ag1e44g7b0cg484d3c318558" version="1">Mirror</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd3ef137g59e7ga3b8gfc48g7e240da2f839" version="1">Mirror implements represent misdirection, illusion, and sleight of hand, bending and shifting a perspective and the way you look at things. While larger mirrors hold the same mystic connotations, thaumaturges always choose small, portable, handheld mirrors as implements so they can use them easily while adventuring. Mirror implements are associated with the harrow suit of keys, and the astrological signs of the stranger and the swallow.</content>
  <content contentuid="h48ea037dg7dbdg9ed5g8700g7f54a77c724a" version="1">Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e5691e9ge107gbbafg3f83g92259918cdc7" version="1">Regalia implements represent rulership, leadership, and social connections. While they differ in shape depending on regional customs and markers used to signify authority, common regalia implements are scepters, jeweled orbs, and heraldic banners. Regalia implements are associated with the harrow suit of crowns and the astrological signs of the patriarch and the sovereign dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcfa0ef68gb400g54fdg50f8g789cfdf4db47" version="1">Tome</content>
  <content contentuid="h61de0bd1g3521ga3c7g9009g6672ad351096" version="1">Tome implements embody lost knowledge and otherworldly insights. While a weathered book is most common, tome implements can have as many different form factors as there are ways to store knowledge, from carved clay tablets to bundles of knotted cords. Tome implements are associated with the harrow suit of books and the astrological signs of the stargazer and the underworld dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h83a6a6abga6dcgd64eg9a66gb6d31bc49e86" version="1">Wand</content>
  <content contentuid="h5526d369g32bbg4977g3271g12e38ca67470" version="1">Wand implements are short, lightweight batons, usually made of wood but often incorporating other materials. Due to their association with spellcasters, wand implements are connected to magic and its practice, as well as the direction and manipulation of energy. Wand implements are associated with the astrological signs of the thrush and the sky dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0f389ea5g6dd2g11a8gfb49g25c87ddd647d" version="1">Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="hd1cbbf97ga21cge43fgb1ddg972f0aaf2b43" version="1">Weapon implements are the most direct and confrontational, representing battle, struggle, and potentially violence. You can choose only a one-handed weapon as an implement, which allows you to channel energies into your weapon as well as hold your other implements once you gain them. Weapon implements are associated with the harrow suit of hammers and the astrological signs of the rider and the swordswoman.</content>
  <content contentuid="h803bf079g9cc5g70efg3282g3b3f5a1c936d" version="1">Thaumaturge</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f570512gecb6gbe0eg6660gdccc7ccbcf12" version="1">The thaumaturge has seen every monster and knows every secret. Supplementing their skill at arms and ability to strike a monster’s weakness with myriad supernatural trinkets and mystic implements that can fill a wide range of roles, the thaumaturge is a versatile agent who can contribute to any team facing the unknown.</content>
  <content contentuid="h205bb61dg5441g3a8eg28d8g394fe1f92a93" version="1">Amulet Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h84564481g9f53g9a80gca82gf37eb49c3483" version="1">Amulets are items carried for good luck and protection. Your amulet might be a magical diagram, a religious symbol, a preserved body part such as a rabbit's foot, or a lucky coin. Amulet implements are associated with the harrow suit of shields and the astrological signs of the bridge and the ogre.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha940f463gb254g53d0g4695g603acb8a5461" version="1">Bell Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h835a6870g8306g1b8fgc2a5gdcfa787ff4a3" version="1">Bells symbolize the power that sounds and emotions hold over others, soothing with one tone and startling with another. Bells, drums, finger cymbals, and other percussion instruments are most typical, but these implements can be any type of portable musical instrument that is played with one hand. Bell implements are associated with the astrological signs of the daughter and the blossom.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0130b7eg773fga704g9fb4gefb0d08ed3f7" version="1">Chalice Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h4843ac2eg0067gff21ga579gd9adc7a3a614" version="1">Chalice implements are vessels that fill with liquid, associating them with healing, nourishment, and life. Your chalice might be a traditional cup or goblet, but it could also be a small amphora, a polished gourd, or even a hollowed-out skull. Chalice implements are associated with the astrological signs of the mother and the newlyweds, as well as the sea dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d886b3egc3fbg037bg2e58g6cc9d82b8531" version="1">Lantern Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="haa0dd64dg6dfdg9088g773bg279f73ef030c" version="1">Lantern implements shine the light of revelation to part shadows and expose truth. You might use a common glass lantern, torch, paper lantern, or other similar light source. Lantern implements are associated with the harrow suit of stars and the astrological signs of the lantern bearer and the archer.</content>
  <content contentuid="he625da99g6d39gcc1cg75f1g36b609113678" version="1">Mirror Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h445facc0g14a3g58afg6e30g2d044439b40c" version="1">Mirror implements represent misdirection, illusion, and sleight of hand, bending and shifting a perspective and the way you look at things. While larger mirrors hold the same mystic connotations, thaumaturges always choose small, portable, handheld mirrors as implements so they can use them easily while adventuring. Mirror implements are associated with the harrow suit of keys, and the astrological signs of the stranger and the swallow.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5b580a88gcb14gc105g02c8g98260694fde8" version="1">Regalia Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h97db613fg1987gc20cg3662ga24b79004d6c" version="1">Regalia implements represent rulership, leadership, and social connections. While they differ in shape depending on regional customs and markers used to signify authority, common regalia implements are scepters, jeweled orbs, and heraldic banners. Regalia implements are associated with the harrow suit of crowns and the astrological signs of the patriarch and the sovereign dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcfa6ed9cg565ag7f78g491fg1dea4309f030" version="1">Tome Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h18bfc33dg29a3g2901g89b2g4d333b4522ae" version="1">Tome implements embody lost knowledge and otherworldly insights. While a weathered book is most common, tome implements can have as many different form factors as there are ways to store knowledge, from carved clay tablets to bundles of knotted cords. Tome implements are associated with the harrow suit of books and the astrological signs of the stargazer and the underworld dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha2a6da91gb864ge572g78cdg590ec20f148e" version="1">Wand Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d891c49g4373g5048g7ecegfb0ddb0acd64" version="1">Wand implements are short, lightweight batons, usually made of wood but often incorporating other materials. Due to their association with spellcasters, wand implements are connected to magic and its practice, as well as the direction and manipulation of energy. Wand implements are associated with the astrological signs of the thrush and the sky dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="hde11f54dga8d9g4e01g0a31g173aea80963c" version="1">Weapon Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h47765644geee6g5740g2e5fgb4639ed1b487" version="1">Weapon implements are the most direct and confrontational, representing battle, struggle, and potentially violence. You can choose only a one-handed weapon as an implement, which allows you to channel energies into your weapon as well as hold your other implements once you gain them. Weapon implements are associated with the harrow suit of hammers and the astrological signs of the rider and the swordswoman.</content>
  <content contentuid="h793767ecg0ae9g049cg69f6g5055d6b4e729" version="1">Exploit Weakness</content>
  <content contentuid="h714678b6g8195gde70g8094g9fd72c08c669" version="1">1 Action &lt;br&gt;Personal Antithesis You improvise a custom weakness on a creature by forcefully presenting and empowering a piece of esoterica that repels it on an individual level; for instance, against a tyrant, you might procure a broken chain that once held a captive. This causes the target creature, and only the target creature, to gain a weakness against your unarmed and weapon Strikes equal to 2 + half your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h21fcea3fg7232g2ac3g0bf7gea0fc3ee32ff" version="1">Implement's Empowerment</content>
  <content contentuid="h54bfbeabg192dg55bbg6950gaf77e43e22e3" version="1">The power of your implement can also be turned to the more common task of combat, its power adding to and amplifying the effects of runes and other magical empowerments. When you Strike, you can trace mystic patterns with an implement you're holding to empower the Strike, causing it to deal 2 additional damage per weapon damage die. Channeling the power requires full use of your hands. You don't gain the benefit of implement's empowerment if you are holding anything in either hand other than a single one-handed weapon, other implements, or esoterica, and you must be holding at least one implement to gain the benefit.&lt;br&gt;This is automatic and is +2 at level 1, +4 at level 4, and +6 at level 12.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8ca3579bg7d30g4eb6g54eagab2e390e9489" version="1">Select Implement</content>
  <content contentuid="h675a1dd0geaa0g598bg1e68g5799300d0bc2" version="1">Exploited Bonuses</content>
  <content contentuid="h261bac52g67b7g7056gfc50g37ea68fa38d1" version="1">You designate a single creature to gain a weakness to you weapon and unarmed attacks equal to [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h8076ca22g8cfag69c2ga8f8g29524832b4e1" version="1">Exploit Weakness</content>
  <content contentuid="h2bb6f450g9438gf0d8gbf1bg0576f09d604c" version="1">Personal Antithesis You improvise a custom weakness on a creature by forcefully presenting and empowering a piece of esoterica that repels it on an individual level; for instance, against a tyrant, you might procure a broken chain that once held a captive. This causes the target creature, and only the target creature, to gain a weakness against your unarmed and weapon Strikes equal to 2 + half your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb9198c4g5cedg1a4dga804gd199e34d4bbd" version="1">Exploited</content>
  <content contentuid="h61ae3b9eg1343g6615g819eg37742c48d0e0" version="1">Affected entity has a weakness against your unarmed and weapon Strikes equal to 2 + half your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h03cbb709gacb0g17fcg8c91gaf572ae68981" version="1">Chalice (Sip)</content>
  <content contentuid="hf4f130cbg415eg1b55g3954gd9e56d1997cb" version="1">Chalice (Sip)</content>
  <content contentuid="h608b50a7gbc5fgaa1ag353agb8a00afa8872" version="1">Sip A sip grants the drinker an amount of temporary Hit Points equal to 2 + half your level that last until the end of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd8d03dagc8f0gc5d0gf555gedcaab0fe0e7" version="1">Chalice (Drain)</content>
  <content contentuid="hf9512c78g49bdgf81bg8916g878593852f52" version="1">Drain (healing, positive) Drinking deep instead heals the drinker 3 Hit Points for each level you have. After the chalice is drained, it's left with only its slowly collecting dregs; the chalice can't be drained again, though it can still be sipped from. If 10 minutes pass without anyone drinking from the chalice, it refills itself and can be drained again. If the drinker has negative healing, it can still heal in this way, and the effect has the negative trait instead of healing and positive.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf3b274a3g760eg38e0gefe0g5ccc12e5f4d2" version="1">Lantern (Light)</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ef6ef2eg88fagb982g5073gc43788f17922" version="1">While you hold your lantern, its burning light leaves secrets no place to hide. You can light or extinguish your lantern as a free action once each turn with nothing but a thought, which has the concentrate trait. The lantern shines bright light out to 20 feet and dim light out 20 feet further; this has the evocation, light, and magical traits (the counteract level against magical darkness is equal to half your level rounded up).</content>
  <content contentuid="h77c4c1ddga7fbgfe9bg636age30fd69d9e19" version="1">Mirror's Reflection</content>
  <content contentuid="h83cea158g7511g4598gdef3g7a2b9b40c5d3" version="1">1 Action&lt;br&gt; You reflect an illusory image of yourself into another unoccupied space within 15 feet that you can see. You are treated as being in both spaces until the start of your next turn. For example, you can attack, Seek, and provide flanking—even with yourself. You occupy both spaces.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcfd27d6fg99aag29cdg31degfedd49550e3e" version="1">Amulet's Abeyance</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e2eea1egfa25g9dccg7bd2g70f784817fb8" version="1">Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability would damage you or an ally within 15 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;Requirements You're holding your amulet implement and are benefiting from Exploit Vulnerability.&lt;br&gt;You forcefully present your amulet to turn away harm. You or a target ally within 15 feet gain resistance to all damage against the triggering damage. The resistance is equal to 2 + your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf3ba6944gfcebg704ag1db5gf22525215768" version="1">Ring Bell (Spell)</content>
  <content contentuid="h43e7ef5fg5ca4g5269gcab6g15e504eda14a" version="1">Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability makes a Strike or Casts a Spell that would affect you or one of your allies.&lt;br&gt;Requirements You are holding your bell implement, and the triggering creature is within 30 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;Distracting Cacophony The trigger is a spell. You create a musical crash of sonic energy that assails the target and breaks its concentration. The target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become stupefied 1 until the end of your next turn (stupefied 2 on a critical failure). The target doesn't have to attempt a flat check to avoid losing the triggering spell, but the discordant ring does lower the spell attack roll or spell DC of the triggering spell from stupefied.</content>
  <content contentuid="h142c8950g9dc6gb1c6g329dge6887a8a1e5e" version="1">Ring Bell (Strike)</content>
  <content contentuid="hcb6676f2g2bbdg975fgc7fbg4f9ad3d06d22" version="1">Trigger The target of your Exploit Vulnerability makes a Strike or Casts a Spell that would affect you or one of your allies.&lt;br&gt;Requirements You are holding your bell implement, and the triggering creature is within 30 feet of you.&lt;br&gt;Disrupting Harmony The trigger is a Strike. You create a strangely discordant harmony that sinks into your foe's mind and throws its movements off. The target must succeed at a Will save against your class DC or become your choice of enfeebled 1 or clumsy 1 until the end of your next turn (enfeebled 2 or clumsy 2 on a critical failure).</content>
  <content contentuid="h726d7604g8dcbg44c2g0d5cg67935cb0abfe" version="1">Mirror (Swap)</content>
  <content contentuid="h63e353f5gd62bga11dg671cgc1c280b4c23f" version="1">Swap places with a mirror duplicate.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd432f4c7ge156gd430g2aaag74bde4911892" version="5">Illusory Double</content>
  <content contentuid="h23bd51e3geabegab25g2b38g0dbee8222c6d" version="1">Fling Magic (Cold)</content>
  <content contentuid="he8e089f0ge24agf10dg43e4g0bc245ccc833" version="1">You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.</content>
  <content contentuid="hab17ebbdgca3cg6e26g3944gfefc377b88d9" version="1">Fling Magic (Fire)</content>
  <content contentuid="h71fe5accg1c62g9a2bg36cbg946c0c464774" version="1">Fling Magic (Electricity)</content>
  <content contentuid="h51e8a5bfg0670g4627g8bafg21d5ec1caadc" version="1">Fling Magic (Cold) Boost</content>
  <content contentuid="hff2d2db3g91c6geaa5gff06g2a7a4f1cb9d3" version="1">Fling Magic (Fire) Boost</content>
  <content contentuid="h534c6a5egeb66gbafege0b0g399c6d883b3c" version="1">Fling Magic (Electricity) Boost</content>
  <content contentuid="h59272a07g2778gbe27g36f4g50854674b918" version="1">Regalia Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h4a4bdc84gd9cagd7f0gead7g8b61699e3436" version="1">The courage your aura instills grows stronger. The +1 status bonus now applies to all saving throws against mental effects, rather than only against fear, and you and allies in your aura gain a +2 status bonus to damage rolls. At 11th level, this increases to a +3 status bonus to damage rolls, and at 17th level, this increases to a +4 status bonus to damage rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb93f9874ge2aag7dc5gcc8fg9c6a1fe36fe5" version="1">Intensify Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="h14e56a07gaf19g4ca7gabb1g589554c082ff" version="1">Your amulet repels the creature's attempts to harm you. You gain a +2 status bonus to AC and saves against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd08b3e8ag25b1g5509g281cg9f6c7dd9f98e" version="1">Intensify Chalice</content>
  <content contentuid="h02759b57g8856g2888g53cfg0769d04d468f" version="1">Your reinforced chalice can collect a creature's life force to become empowered. If you succeed at a Strike against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you increase the effect if someone Drinks from the Chalice before the end of that turn. Add an additional half your level to the temporary HP if the drinker sips, or add your level to the HP regained if the drinker drains the chalice. This effect isn't cumulative if you hit with more than one Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5b52e905geec6g6a77g48d4gb3149f7c0e83" version="1">Intensify Mirror</content>
  <content contentuid="hebed587cgf00bga809g2c65g80dbc580c1ca" version="1">Reinforcing your mirror lets it play tricks on your enemy's senses as it bends light this way or that. You become concealed to the target of your Exploit Vulnerability as your mirror warps its perceptions. As normal for concealment where your overall location is still obvious, you can't use this concealment to Hide or Sneak.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0bfcca8dg1a8fgfe15ge9c9g60385c54a63d" version="1">Intensify Tome</content>
  <content contentuid="hbecf337eg7a58g94c3g9969g44197262457a" version="1">Your tome's power not only reads a creature's present but even records its future actions. When you use Intensify Vulnerability, roll a d20 and set the result aside. At any time until the start of your next turn, you can use the d20 result you set aside for an attack roll to Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, instead of rolling a new d20; this is a fortune effect.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbac6351cg3554g14e1ga437gc3ae38448f38" version="1">Intensify Wand</content>
  <content contentuid="h679cf409g4c4dg6b1ag28eeg510bdbee1108" version="1">Your empowered wand surges with ever-more-powerful magic. When you Fling Magic to damage the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you deal additional damage to the creature equal to 1 + the number of damage dice.</content>
  <content contentuid="h26bb7652gb6e4g00a6g35e3gde86756a03c9" version="1">Intensify Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="h9cabd202g40c2gf010g2f67g5a463e7c3a07" version="1">Your weapon is drawn to your enemy's vital spots, almost of its own accord. You gain a +2 status bonus to attack rolls against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="he0b003f7gb16egd518g31b2g342613c3a7c9" version="1">Tome Recall</content>
  <content contentuid="h6e304826gaa3dgb03cg2791ge29ffce75976" version="1">In addition to the initiate benefits, your tome inscribes insights into creatures that you can use to strike them down. While holding your tome, at the start of your turn each round, attempt a check to Recall Knowledge about a creature of your choice that you're observing. If this check succeeds, you gain a +1 circumstance bonus to your next attack roll against that creature before the start of your next turn.&lt;br&gt;BG3: Persuasion versus Perception.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb831a78cge18cgb458gf9b0gc350bc53105e" version="1">Intensify Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="hcd3d65edg7207g3baag9d01g9c38101e532f" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round, or a –3 status penalty on a critical hit. This effect has the auditory, emotion, and mental traits.</content>
  <content contentuid="h61d96a5bge233g4d82g73adgfd84d4acd2dd" version="1">Intensify Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h40dd9b0bg53dag35fdg3b2fg66714453ea8d" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, choose an ally that you can see. That ally gains a +1 circumstance bonus to its attack rolls against the creature until the beginning of your next turn. If the attack roll was a critical hit, the circumstance bonus increases to +2.</content>
  <content contentuid="he483ea5fg74f7g969eg6b12geea630c27dac" version="1">Amulet Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="h7becaf7agebf8g7443ge065gda2954348420" version="1">Your amulet offers continued protection. When you use Amulet's Abeyance, you or your ally chooses one type of damage dealt by the triggering attack and gains resistance 5 against that damage type until the start of your next turn. At 15th level, this lingering resistance increases from 5 to 10.</content>
  <content contentuid="h21fb36b6gf4aagc052g2083ge4d76e74b6c2" version="1">Chalice Adept Bonus</content>
  <content contentuid="hb4da3524g52fdg8f08gba7agf2c93fce88f5" version="1">The life essence shed from blood empowers your chalice. If you or an ally within 30 feet takes piercing or slashing damage from a foe's critical hit or takes persistent bleed damage, Drinking from the Chalice before the end of your next turn grants that injured creature greater restoration to make up for its lost vitality. On a sip, the temporary Hit Points granted to the creature increase to 2 + your Charisma modifier + your level. When drained, the chalice heals the creature 5 Hit Points for each level you have.</content>
  <content contentuid="h81f45380gaafbg3d9eg791ag86c8f49dd5bf" version="1">Mirror Shatter</content>
  <content contentuid="h38724484g4911ge171geb2dg02b82cb94401" version="1">Your mirror self shatters into punishing shards when damaged. While Mirror's Reflection is in effect, when an enemy adjacent to one of your spaces damages you, that version of you explodes into mirror shards. This ends Mirror's Reflection (establishing the remaining version of you as the real one) and deals slashing damage to all creatures in a 5-foot emanation around where your mirror self was. The damage is equal to 2 + half your level or the damage of the triggering attack, whichever is lower. You're immune to this damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc444ed28g7851ge07eg2352g003e0a755c5b" version="1">Intensify Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h74a753dbg36d7g20f6gd969g4dc15d027735" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, they have a -1 circumstance penalty to AC until the beginning of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0eb5dd3eg6574g5e17g2699g1e19589e2d7b" version="1">Intensify Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="h47be1468g8a6egd172g0f83g138fc170d828" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="h4c2ccc6eg1cbegc434g392eg0252668d669e" version="1">%%% EMPTY</content>
  <content contentuid="h792ba08dgfe32g9c83g9c4bg9704fb7b3453" version="1">Portent Dice</content>
  <content contentuid="h6200122egfb98g1630g4ef4ga182089f5c8c" version="1">Affected entity possesses the power to influence the future through divination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entity can use a reaction to change the die of any &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; rolled nearby to a [1].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonuses and penalties will still be added to the number.</content>
  <content contentuid="h326c2d20gc8edg9307g2dd5ge1483c265664" version="1">Intensified Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="h668a34e5gbec9gbedege67dgdf2d56fe4579" version="1">Your weapon is drawn to your enemy's vital spots, almost of its own accord. You gain a +2 status bonus to attack rolls against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="h59e123a1g3dbeg9791g39acge1d81b460810" version="1">Intensified Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="h00192464g6d40gb912g576dg2e7f613d9129" version="1">Your amulet repels the creature's attempts to harm you. You gain a +2 status bonus to AC and saves against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="h320cfa58gd4e5g9398g6c74gd6d1696d3b82" version="1">Intensified Wand</content>
  <content contentuid="hd4beefc2g491cg3f6cgb36dg327975edd560" version="1">Your empowered wand surges with ever-more-powerful magic. When you Fling Magic to damage the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you deal additional damage to the creature equal to 1 + the number of damage dice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb285973dg450cg0f87gf020ga13d472390fb" version="1">Intensified Chalice</content>
  <content contentuid="hee7ebce2g9119g3fe6g378eg4dfed22925c4" version="1">Your reinforced chalice can collect a creature's life force to become empowered. If you succeed at a Strike against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you increase the effect if someone Drinks from the Chalice before the end of that turn. Add an additional half your level to the temporary HP if the drinker sips, or add your level to the HP regained if the drinker drains the chalice. This effect isn't cumulative if you hit with more than one Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc4e8a22cg60e2g09e0g8159gd62f8fa14aa8" version="1">Intensified Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h9bf7d36ag6db1gf05fg475bg184d9bca1161" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, they have a -1 circumstance penalty to AC until the beginning of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5a5d9119g94e4g5549g309fgf5c950e42bb0" version="1">Intensified Bell (Debuff)</content>
  <content contentuid="h4ef08f99g07b9geb6fg3dcdg630782490a16" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="he6611890g7337g6eddge888g9124f8206756" version="1">Intensified Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="h424c3bd6g4ffcg2722gb529gff90c8f13625" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="h45422406gcca1gb873g1abcgacf4c0caef67" version="1">Bellstruck</content>
  <content contentuid="h76fc9edbg646bg13d6g3c38g0675df3ed691" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="hf93978beg2161gc488gcdc3g52b1953ca972" version="1">Portent Die: 1</content>
  <content contentuid="h7b7c80d0g83b8gd333g986eg2ba0245f4dbb" version="1">Change the die of a nearby &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt; to [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h1c1d934bgb383gf88cg0333g749a6e55ec7d" version="1">Bonuses and penalties will still be added to the number.</content>
  <content contentuid="h848ad874ga30dgb17bg41ddg34944e3114a8" version="1">Wand Initiate (Cold)</content>
  <content contentuid="ha3365451g0333gd9fbga6e4gf60565ddcbb5" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27052479g325cgbf7cg9203ge1166f15e9d3" version="1">Wand Initiate (Electricity)</content>
  <content contentuid="h9887bb46ge295g6053gb537gb5fa3b3321ff" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5a6f32d4g651bgb84dg72e0g14d2f248820e" version="1">Wand Initiate (Boost)</content>
  <content contentuid="h3809f698gcd96gb73bg1a88gc61556f72743" version="1">Wand Initiate (Boost)</content>
  <content contentuid="h87910704gfef2gb3f5gbff3g5be85cb68b0b" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="h86f29909g9d4agca52gf7fcgcd93c4a47c2f" version="1">Wand Initiate (Boost)</content>
  <content contentuid="h52946b3fga634gbfefg8eb0gbec00b09301c" version="1">Your wand slowly collects ambient magic, which you can project at a foe in a barely controlled display of charged energy. When you gain this implement, choose whether your wand is attuned to cold, electricity, or fire. You gain the Fling Magic activity.&lt;br&gt;2 Actions&lt;br&gt;You fling magical energy at a target within 60 feet, dealing damage equal to 1d4 + your Charisma modifier to the target, with a basic Reflex save against your class DC. The damage is of the type you selected when you gained your wand implement. At 3rd level and every 2 levels thereafter, the damage increases by 1d4.&lt;br&gt;You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally. If you critically hit with a Strike, your wand recharges immediately as it draws in power from the clash.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7a8a3b83gba23gf21fgb6fcge76f03111999" version="1">Exploited</content>
  <content contentuid="h51a54bd4g51dag1a84gb8c5g9b7a67b3828d" version="1">Affected entity has a weakness against your unarmed and weapon Strikes equal to 2 + half your level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcffaf29cg394dgde39g0c60g257ed7603575" version="1">Chalice (Sip)</content>
  <content contentuid="h49f32135gb505g1da9g2da6g2c35464793a9" version="1">Amulet Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1a40027gf050g208dgda70g57b8907a4ebb" version="1">Your amulet offers continued protection. When you use Amulet's Abeyance, you or your ally chooses one type of damage dealt by the triggering attack and gains resistance 5 against that damage type until the start of your next turn. At 15th level, this lingering resistance increases from 5 to 10.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd3ee20cg03d6g7cc2g14e3gaa2209049825" version="1">Chalice Adept Bonus</content>
  <content contentuid="h3818fc1dg9153g8545g1101gd5e74794e967" version="1">The life essence shed from blood empowers your chalice. If you or an ally within 30 feet takes piercing or slashing damage from a foe's critical hit or takes persistent bleed damage, Drinking from the Chalice before the end of your next turn grants that injured creature greater restoration to make up for its lost vitality. On a sip, the temporary Hit Points granted to the creature increase to 2 + your Charisma modifier + your level. When drained, the chalice heals the creature 5 Hit Points for each level you have.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf7db0c64g024egb110ge4a1g3ef615aa4275" version="1">%%% EMPTY</content>
  <content contentuid="hf4841586g0e57g4cf3g8408g2b5b335f2599" version="1">Portent Dice</content>
  <content contentuid="h054c6f37ga984g2a72g3459gb9a6fb18f3a7" version="1">Affected entity possesses the power to influence the future through divination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entity can use a reaction to change the die of any &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; rolled nearby to a [1].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonuses and penalties will still be added to the number.</content>
  <content contentuid="heb79ed83gac02ga389ga2cbg79c10d634fc1" version="1">Intensified Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="hd2ba9536g5074gca5dg3989g51fc874f548e" version="1">Your weapon is drawn to your enemy's vital spots, almost of its own accord. You gain a +2 status bonus to attack rolls against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcab75b1fgbde3gcff3g0b4fg03a2bfebe7e5" version="1">Intensified Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd2c5dbegbbb3g12c8ge41cge404fc64db94" version="1">Your amulet repels the creature's attempts to harm you. You gain a +2 status bonus to AC and saves against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability.</content>
  <content contentuid="h144c571dg98a5g6625g4ac7g413041c835ba" version="1">Intensified Wand</content>
  <content contentuid="h033747b7g5c0fg16b2g13e6g3d61fde453e4" version="1">Your empowered wand surges with ever-more-powerful magic. When you Fling Magic to damage the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you deal additional damage to the creature equal to 1 + the number of damage dice.</content>
  <content contentuid="he38ed122g9afdgbff3gf566gb3273249b404" version="1">Intensified Chalice</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d84efa9g9d45g75fdgcbb3g5b384c9c5083" version="1">Your reinforced chalice can collect a creature's life force to become empowered. If you succeed at a Strike against the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, you increase the effect if someone Drinks from the Chalice before the end of that turn. Add an additional half your level to the temporary HP if the drinker sips, or add your level to the HP regained if the drinker drains the chalice. This effect isn't cumulative if you hit with more than one Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8674b07ag201fg4addg6b37g5f1cd1893451" version="1">Intensified Regalia</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ca6cc4fg0d0eg614dg91e8g533967486f7f" version="1">Your regalia implement makes you seem more confident and inspiring with each success. Whenever you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, they have a -1 circumstance penalty to AC until the beginning of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0ef536agd1f7g54e3g7e61gcee9996a383a" version="1">Intensified Bell (Debuff)</content>
  <content contentuid="hc6293187g3bcbg4398gde15g7b33073d5af5" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="h70ecdc1eg994fg7f5eg0d19g1cbccd884da8" version="1">Intensified Bell</content>
  <content contentuid="hab31e938gde9fg0ed6g2241gd682e8826b91" version="1">Your reinforced bell can reach into the most basal part of the target's mind, priming it to be vulnerable to the bell's effects. When you successfully Strike the target of your Exploit Vulnerability, your bell implement plays a haunting tone and the creature takes a –2 status penalty on saves against your Ring Bell for 1 round</content>
  <content contentuid="h13a26d10ge2fdg34a7gbae3g765c92b4338f" version="1">Wand Boost (Ready)</content>
  <content contentuid="h3a88d388g4802ga124g3cccg0e4ddd46b7d0" version="1">You can expend more energy than usual to boost the effect of Fling Magic, dealing d6s of damage instead of d4s. After you do so, the wand takes 1d4 rounds to recharge, during which you can't boost the wand's damage but can continue to Fling Magic normally</content>
  <content contentuid="h5d0da5d1gd30bg5981g852bgcf0e3a5664a3" version="2">Attenuated Attire</content>
  <content contentuid="h1a6bc16fgf36eg1e02g5257gcb3c57ff6a2a" version="2">Light enough to feel the elements flow freely and thick enough to withstand them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2cc3593dg54efg93d3g56d5gd62af1abeeae" version="1">Kineticist</content>
  <content contentuid="ha96ca59bgbdeagac3bgfeacgd4253cc9a2db" version="1">Select Gate</content>
  <content contentuid="h0327922fg41dfgbd6bgced8g300e7d28df73" version="1">The power of the elements flows from within you. Roaring fire, pure water, fleeting air, steadfast earth, twisting wood, slicing metal. A kinetic gate inextricably tied to your body channels power directly from the elemental planes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h88d3aadcgac8cg0bfbg44a8g3c38912100c4" version="1">Air</content>
  <content contentuid="hdf9be300gff21gd1c7gd40ag3e5138cbe880" version="1">Earth</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f19d87dgca0eg1102g519ag8c688b96bb5c" version="1">Earth Fragments of stone float around you, granting you a +1 circumstance bonus to AC until the start of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha60635f9ge884g448egb5c3g390a08146839" version="1">Fire</content>
  <content contentuid="h2f8de5ddg513eg5c43g14e3g2be620b18e42" version="1">Fire Increase the damage die size of fire damage dealt by the impulse by one step.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f4a7a8bg3169g56deg1702gb44dc17ed7b7" version="1">Water</content>
  <content contentuid="h0a8b785agae9agb1d4g4bd8ge282b2a88d58" version="1">Water After the impulse's other effects, you can move one creature targeted by the impulse or in its area 5 feet in any direction, or 10 feet if it's in a body of water. This can't move the creature into the air. You can choose only a creature that's willing to be moved, that failed its save against the impulse, or that you succeeded at an impulse attack roll against.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3e82d169gcd83gb1fbge2fagaeab3c6ef6ef" version="1">Wood</content>
  <content contentuid="hc3ba8d5dg6335g3e9egdd70g15332ae9f05a" version="1">Wood You gain temporary Hit Points equal to your level that last until the start of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h974ac47fgcb64g5b9bgc5a3gfaaadeb75fdb" version="1">Metal</content>
  <content contentuid="hdb8077cagb7c3g8914gb681g730ba80fd2a7" version="1">Metal Choose acid, electricity, or piercing. Until the start of your next turn, each time a creature touches you or damages you with an unarmed melee attack or non-reach melee weapon, it takes damage of the chosen type equal to half your level (minimum 1 damage).</content>
  <content contentuid="haa2edbe2g40b7gb575ge72fge99107637d86" version="1">Dual Gate</content>
  <content contentuid="h5265d891g588bg4a19g51ecg7dc308358a7b" version="2">Your kinetic gate is a harmonious conduit between two planes, allowing you to combine their elements to give you a versatile set of abilities.</content>
  <content contentuid="h294d267cga6f8ga626g96a9g491b4884a01a" version="2">Intensified Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9a5c763g6dedgba95g1c0egac574ea3d70e" version="1">Intensified Lantern</content>
  <content contentuid="h082dbb05ge8ccg79d0gce1bg7a587b0a1531" version="1">When you Strike and deal damage to a creature while your lantern is intensified, remove concealed and invisibility effects.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27b89719ge354gb185g4fe6gf2c9d31f87c1" version="1">Divine Disharmony</content>
  <content contentuid="h441dd006geeedg2d37g312eg6a9d2b9f1ad9" version="1">Root to Life</content>
  <content contentuid="h761c37b1g6fb6g5d7cg590dg3fef35138266" version="1">Scroll Thaumaturgy</content>
  <content contentuid="h41bd3d7cge5fcg554ag4f93gad95bf1f790e" version="1">Scroll Esoterica</content>
  <content contentuid="h03b0ff5egbc85gbf4cg753fg8673a4966add" version="1">Cursed Effigy</content>
  <content contentuid="h87fc3bd5g5949g6889g5159gd92a7b908a5f" version="1">Share Weakness</content>
  <content contentuid="h9b9a8a88gf0fegdddag7422g3151f951bc25" version="1">Twin Weakness</content>
  <content contentuid="hd7b43132ge19ag4093g3bccg39ba2e461184" version="1">Elaborate Scroll Esoterica</content>
  <content contentuid="h52aab529gc328gbe09gc4d3g728eec843bbd" version="1">ChaliceSipStatusAdept</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d9ab60bg4ecdg9f20g8f07g370962dc8b82" version="1">IntenseChalice</content>
  <content contentuid="h303a2cacg9eebg35eeg26d1g5cd4b3f5025c" version="1">LanternLightStatus</content>
  <content contentuid="he6aa5167gbb08g139fg559egf7fb1e5af1ca" version="1">MirrorCloneStatus</content>
  <content contentuid="h2ea38236g98b5gcc28g1e42ge87015160533" version="1">MirrorHPShare</content>
  <content contentuid="h1b671055g10c0g4334g6f0bg396dc2bc5a11" version="1">MirrorHPShareSelf</content>
  <content contentuid="h61939ce0ge422g494dg3892g517f7e5af17e" version="1">Bell Penalties</content>
  <content contentuid="h9fbb9972g2594ge925g9086g284e6161427f" version="1">Backswing Infusion</content>
  <content contentuid="h432ce3c9g2929gdc98gf3b6g503d9ae36652" version="1">You can use the momentum from a missed attack with this weapon to lead into your next attack. After missing with this weapon on your turn, you gain a +1 circumstance bonus to your next attack with this weapon before the end of your turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h096d7445gf10ag836dg3ff9g8146038cd2cd" version="1">You can use the momentum from a missed attack with this weapon to lead into your next attack. After missing with this weapon on your turn, you gain a +1 circumstance bonus to your next attack with this weapon before the end of your turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h73d420f8g9b73g3113gfa50g20186810bf92" version="1">Intensified Mirror</content>
  <content contentuid="ha50ccabag0278g8629g9ae4g411edd8d16f9" version="1">Reinforcing your mirror lets it play tricks on your enemy's senses as it bends light this way or that. You become concealed to the target of your Exploit Vulnerability as your mirror warps its perceptions. As normal for concealment where your overall location is still obvious, you can't use this concealment to Hide or Sneak.</content>
  <content contentuid="h78516bc5gae9ag7539g3b55g81bea871c3d7" version="1">Remove Kineticist Armor</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f7bc3a0ga057ge464g8bb5g8166a3b6d365" version="1">You can use this ability to remove your kineticist impulse armor</content>
  <content contentuid="hc02c4801g21dag5b38gfd05gaa6ace95c9e4" version="1">Removed Kineticist Armor</content>
  <content contentuid="h8af283e4g40a0g732eg4c94gb010fc397415" version="1">Shield Block </content>
  <content contentuid="hfba7bec3gd050g9fabgf51ag63f645b1e49e" version="1">While you have a shield &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_RaiseShield"&gt;raised&lt;/LSTag&gt;, reduce the damage of a weapon attack by [1]. </content>
  <content contentuid="h8ff2d714g38cagfc8egbff9g8e8b4dedb0a2" version="1">Raise a Shield </content>
  <content contentuid="h7721161bg39c0g623bg7365gefd0d8b81e9e" version="1">You position your shield to protect yourself. When you have Raised a Shield, you gain its listed circumstance bonus to AC. Your shield remains raised until the start of your next turn. </content>
  <content contentuid="h96c6119ega8fdga880g86ddg3e425002f197" version="1">Shield Block  </content>
  <content contentuid="h7e2540a5ga97dg3664gf5d5g04b0e85a79c3" version="1">While you have a shield &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_RaiseShield"&gt;raised&lt;/LSTag&gt;, reduce the damage of a weapon attack by [1].  </content>
  <content contentuid="he32ab8f0gbaaeg749ag83d6g75002015ef32" version="1">You can use the momentum from a missed attack with this weapon to lead into your next attack. After missing with this weapon on your turn, you gain a +1 circumstance bonus to your next attack with this weapon before the end of your turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hebd9609bgbbbeg14d7g0af7g21de401a4eaf" version="1">Backswing Infusion</content>
  <content contentuid="h3bf2d1f6gca48g961cg38ddga20a032eb0f9" version="1">You can use the momentum from a missed attack with this weapon to lead into your next attack. After missing with this weapon on your turn, you gain a +1 circumstance bonus to your next attack with this weapon before the end of your turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h49f3b4c2g18c4gec35gd5d3gc2642e1c5139" version="1">Your Kinetic Aura is already active.</content>
  <content contentuid="he9985273g180eg423fg6b46g131b9ad60a06" version="1">Strength: 14</content>
  <content contentuid="hd70ed20dg45b7ga294gb3e9g44c858a4ac0f" version="1">Throwing Potency</content>
  <content contentuid="h2449e583g7164g0fdeg5824g605a7cd41763" version="1">You have a +[1] bonus to thrown item attack rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3848663dg89f1gaa7agf74bg6b44067bec81" version="1">Greater Throwing Potency</content>
  <content contentuid="hf24f4561g9177gb976geb2ag0eef5b904a0f" version="1">Quick Bomber</content>
  <content contentuid="h4cd5805agf797g108bg4c7eg96e278482913" version="1">Throw an infused item.</content>
  <content contentuid="h09cfc44dg3d29g351ag81e6g8d9d57c85b6e" version="2">Craft a temporary consumable. &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; Alchemy makes BG3 versions of alchemical items</content>
  <content contentuid="h3eff46d0g6ce8g893eg5d62g2381e2a8e60b" version="3">Can be performed as a free action after using &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_QuickAlchemy"&gt;Quick Alchemy&lt;/LSTag&gt;. If you can create multiple bombs at a time, you can only Strike with one.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5ceb1888g5adege7fdg518egd322ce8ac377" version="1">Double Brew</content>
  <content contentuid="hba605acbgab1cg4f0ag5f93gba9e325609f2" version="1">Can use an additional vial as a free action.</content>
  <content contentuid="h470b0ee8ga9a0ga478g09c7gf3be3a743caf" version="1">Quick Bomber</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd9f95ccg9725g2a90g871fgf148de8fe119" version="1">You can create and throw a bomb in a single action.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0d6d84ag5904g212fg92f1gd77c3ed82e3b" version="1">Applies to &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_VersatileVial"&gt;thrown vials&lt;/LSTag&gt; and bombs made with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_QuickAlchemy"&gt;Quick Alchemy&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="had12512bg7a01gcc7cg2cb5gff34e7b8e16c" version="1">Double Brew</content>
  <content contentuid="hc138789dgfcdeg0d1ag6a1ageb9bec608cd5" version="1">When using &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_QuickAlchemy"&gt;Quick Alchemy&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_VersatileVial"&gt;quick vials&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you can create two items at once.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6cfc85a4gbf0fge646ge9cag430618d10537" version="2">You still expend &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="VersatileVial"&gt;versatile vials&lt;/LSTag&gt; to make consumables.</content>
  <content contentuid="h722756bag2d16g6f5bg87cdgf55a0e5ff91c" version="1">Quick Bomber</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ec5b4f8ga6d7gacb8gede4gf3c1473a2106" version="1">Can throw as a free action.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd8b7602gf9b8g5b1cgc26eg83c53cca70ab" version="1">Alchemical Assessment</content>
  <content contentuid="h2b7e9db3g620dg14e5gf941g6ebe059bb15f" version="1">You can easily identify alchemical components. You learn the formula for every alchemical item or extract you find, as well as all common related recipes.</content>
  <content contentuid="he5d96d9fg4ac3gebfbg79f7g8fc0279b8667" version="1">Select Research Field</content>
  <content contentuid="h6356fdb4gdfa6g8b60gca0bgd9803d192e4b" version="1">Infused Reagents</content>
  <content contentuid="hb4692ddcg8341g16f9gd6adgacbef436129b" version="1">You can craft a number of alchemical items each day equal to [3] plus your Intelligence modifier.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4fc184cag1da4g47cegb40cg95c7ea4dc7e7" version="1">Versatile Vials</content>
  <content contentuid="h24181deeg36abg7a1dge4d2g692a3fc4767c" version="1">Versatile vials can be used in battle to create short-lived consumables. You can supply two vials per short rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd2b970c6gbf6egdedbg6d6fgb1f34b154519" version="1">Alchemical Expertise</content>
  <content contentuid="h0fc91c2dg74ccg9baegfa42gca523fdabea6" version="1">You gain an additional &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="VersatileVial"&gt;versatile vial&lt;/LSTag&gt; to craft with.</content>
  <content contentuid="haa429205g1ca7gf51ega5a8g88cb5b85cf38" version="1">Impulse</content>
  <content contentuid="h3cd4319fg8012g3ae8gf536g6a4b61b18a03" version="2">An impulse is a special type of magical action available to kineticists, allowing them to wield or shape their element into diverse and powerful forms. To wield an element, you must have your kinetic aura active and have a free hand. You can select an impulse feat only if it matches one of your kinetic elements.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5819fee9g1936g31fageff7g640f15f3687a" version="1">Smart and resourceful, the alchemist crafts alchemical items—such as bombs, elixirs, and poisons—that they use to defeat foes and aid allies.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf144cd2dg876egef67g08aegf89577ca5370" version="1">Bomber</content>
  <content contentuid="hf750d899g4d8bgf7acg180fg194d04cf8281" version="1">You specialize in explosions and other violent reactions.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbeca8394g9395g8b83g72c0g8a013b89cc09" version="1">Chirurgeon</content>
  <content contentuid="ha1f1b805gb30ag970eg5c7agae8234f1169c" version="1">You concentrate on healing others with alchemy.</content>
  <content contentuid="h52160e24g06b3g8dfcg39b4g824c2b1c1042" version="1">Toxicologist</content>
  <content contentuid="hef23d4d2gc4e5g1b46ge759g4df83a54b083" version="1">You specialize in toxins and venoms of all types.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6b75d14cgf3beg3976g1409g68f22ff86c83" version="1">Calculated Splash</content>
  <content contentuid="h7b230bbcgda9fg7873gaa4fgca3073df8e4f" version="3">When you throw a bomb, the splash damage doesn't affect you or your allies.</content>
  <content contentuid="h37441c7dgee16g2da8g8b23g5a646a9ba404" version="2">Calculated Splash</content>
  <content contentuid="h741c6302g62d9g2329ga06dgf69c2a62d28a" version="1">When you throw a bomb, increase the splash damage to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt; modifier if it's lower.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha40381cagaa83gba87g5ed7g8bac5deb549f" version="1">Corporis Fabrica</content>
  <content contentuid="hb112cfccg71b5g4afegf030g8325e1d4a886" version="1">You can use &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Nature"&gt;Crafting&lt;/LSTag&gt; instead of &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Medicine"&gt;Medicine&lt;/LSTag&gt; for &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SkillCheck"&gt;Skill Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; and requirements.</content>
  <content contentuid="h86a39c50g500agd1bcgc6c0g516918bc990f" version="1">Pharmacopoeia</content>
  <content contentuid="h8886d476g4e5ega443g2ef0g52cbc4b7afd6" version="1">When a creature drinks an &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ALCH_INFUSED"&gt;infused&lt;/LSTag&gt; healing item you created, they gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;temporary hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt; modifier for 1 minute.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e0613b1g5515ge115g19e0g7848db446d56" version="1">Anticoagulation</content>
  <content contentuid="heddac2e3g162eg501egd279ge247ea08dd58" version="1">When you use a field vial to heal a creature that has half its maximum &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; or fewer, the coagulant trait doesn’t apply.</content>
  <content contentuid="h66c41210g1dfdgbe5bgabecg2ccd4dc3cbeb" version="1">Corrosive Venom</content>
  <content contentuid="h6582be19gc928g19c4g4376g9dec0dd291dc" version="1">Attacks you make ignore resistance and immunity to Poison damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9f6b25f7g8b7fg7f44g81a4gd1b7abd9a748" version="1">Flexible Mixture</content>
  <content contentuid="he1a80742g671bgc8d5gbc86g0310c20c42db" version="1">You can &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Dip"&gt;Dip&lt;/LSTag&gt; your weapon in a surface as a free action.</content>
  <content contentuid="h218a5c7eg96d1g03a0g3bd4gcb7fa4b7922f" version="1">Lingering Poison</content>
  <content contentuid="hf513963dgb9c7g14a2gd228g6698927b53f5" version="1">When you damage a creature with a field vial you’ve used as an injury poison, that creature takes persistent poison damage equal to the vial’s splash damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf925f11ag13b1gb178g0d10g9ee03a7835a7" version="1">Ingenious Elixir</content>
  <content contentuid="h4b3f1686ge97dg1561ga5c6gab9d6914ecb9" version="1">When you drink an elixir, you gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;temporary hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt; modifier for 1 minute.</content>
  <content contentuid="haa7051bfg62f9gb308g720eg55743842dfab" version="1">Altered Biochemistry</content>
  <content contentuid="hd9c33bedg4bb4gc5c8g9834g5c3f650e990a" version="1">When you roll a Fortitude save while affected by an elixir, you can end the effect of the elixir to reroll the save.</content>
  <content contentuid="h89e80e62g7cbag7ea8g82c0g0d5254b13d40" version="1">Clotting Elixirs</content>
  <content contentuid="he166241fg0263g9b3bgf2f3g0ef3c299d3b6" version="1">When a creature drinks an &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ALCH_INFUSED"&gt;infused&lt;/LSTag&gt; healing item you created, it can attempt a DC 10 flat check to stop any &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLEEDING"&gt;persistent bleed damage&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h86180733gb6b6gd8c2g45f8gbf3c2c0af972" version="1">Quarrel Poisoner</content>
  <content contentuid="h148748e0g215dg13d4gfe43gf08cc1c6ad1c" version="1">Your hand crossbow Strikes apply injury poisons on a hit, even if no damage is dealt. On a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="CriticalHit"&gt;critical hit&lt;/LSTag&gt;, the target automatically fails their &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;save&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d41ffb5gd1c7g0c5eg3cf7gc0bf2b6caaee" version="1">When you Strike with a hand crossbow while &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="HIDDEN"&gt;hidden&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you roll a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Stealth"&gt;Stealth&lt;/LSTag&gt; check instead of automatically becoming observed.</content>
  <content contentuid="he981c3b7g0735g7391gddc1ge4c511cf0b12" version="1">Precise Trajectory</content>
  <content contentuid="ha334fa19gebdcg04deg6d3dg7d8d7aa14b3c" version="1">The negative effects of surfaces, such as &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BURNING"&gt;fire&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ACID"&gt;acid&lt;/LSTag&gt;, or exploding grease, still apply.</content>
  <content contentuid="hce31a04agb93fgc733g3e06g9ec359a3d088" version="1">Far Lobber</content>
  <content contentuid="hbc19d6b8g77cfgf561g5603g511dee74ebb7" version="1">Clotting Elixir</content>
  <content contentuid="h9cd37241gdc2dg790fg9173g40ec530a9195" version="1">Coagulant</content>
  <content contentuid="h60ab2180g322dg8da8gaef9gc85fe495de92" version="1">Can't restore &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; from alchemical coagulants until the next &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc4d454a8gce67g5811g9da0g5c4581a7b4c4" version="1">Field Vials: Healing</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e68c25ag9de7g7732gac38gdea435b4bf3b" version="1">Throw a versatile vial to heal a living creature.</content>
  <content contentuid="h438fb79dg325fga56ag7ce7gc38951acda7c" version="1">Altered Biochemistry</content>
  <content contentuid="h85e81279g7871gd2ecgc1f2g1f9ba344668b" version="1">When you roll a Fortitude save while affected by an elixir, you can end the effect of the elixir to reroll the save.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf19d6cf0ga82cg42d9g4dfag6ffe8707ee4d" version="1">Revivifying Mutagen</content>
  <content contentuid="h0dd3a909g1273g24c7gccb3ge2b300380879" version="1">Metabolize an elixir to heal yourself [1], ending its effects.</content>
  <content contentuid="hba84928dg86cag7571g8ce2g78516e993d08" version="1">Revivifying Mutagen</content>
  <content contentuid="h5289629dgeec3ge622g20b8gab3364d8354c" version="1">Metabolize an elixir to heal yourself, ending its effects.</content>
  <content contentuid="h18948c34g949ag749fg2346g551c0cb062b2" version="1">Must be under the effects of an elixir.</content>
  <content contentuid="h36369336g65e0g2348g2254g187780837444" version="1">Demolition Charge</content>
  <content contentuid="hdf4a8571gcc4bge35dg3ba7g2a1cb3b06961" version="1">Deploy a barrel of smokepowder that explodes when lit.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7a832fb5g49dag1d9cg8d3bg8104d2a8c090" version="1">Demolition Charge</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c4096b0g71d0g5644g3ea2g2da681870c9f" version="1">While exploring, you can deploy a barrel of smokepowder that explodes when lit.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb32f0100gb3b6g84fcgdcebg3a05d603eaf3" version="1">Improvise Admixture</content>
  <content contentuid="he63c49f9g5094ga63agc938g0a0b2e871f29" version="1">Attempt a DC [1] &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Nature"&gt;Crafting&lt;/LSTag&gt; check to recover your &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="VersatileVial"&gt;versatile vials&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h475503f7ga39fg9e60g8fbcg4a25ad03e21d" version="1">Smoke Bomb</content>
  <content contentuid="h5d1ba9beg1f6bg5928gacc5g36534ee50378" version="2">Add a tarry additive to an alchemical bomb. When thrown, it creates a [1] cloud that conceals creatures within it.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha2d4bdf1g3226gf558ge5bcgef6286cac075" version="1">Smoke Bomb</content>
  <content contentuid="h0f25f945gca58g293eg0ccagee000d5b324a" version="1">When thrown, it creates a cloud that conceals creatures within it.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfda649bagd516gda9cg8fbcg3763d140c1a7" version="1">Improvise Admixture</content>
  <content contentuid="h8028af82g8ecfg265dga7b1g24dace232642" version="1">Attempt a DC [1] &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Nature"&gt;Crafting&lt;/LSTag&gt; check to recover your &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="VersatileVial"&gt;versatile vials&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="he245552fgc59dg45ffgb632gdd59f0ff019e" version="1">Restores two on a success, three on a critical success, and one on a non-critical failure.</content>
  <content contentuid="h10560044ge923g4eedg1ceag6fa2ff352920" version="1">Shaped Contaminant</content>
  <content contentuid="h66c7c9a1g2523g81a4ga6adg129eaaebe1c0" version="1">You can brew an inhaled poison and deploy it in a [1] line. Affected creatures take [2] every turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1a81c681g94cbg1158g434agf69e39b42ed8" version="1">Uncanny Bombs</content>
  <content contentuid="h0cd4f1d6g7ca7g7faag452fg22d0c69fb850" version="1">You lob bombs unerringly, despite obstructions or distance. Double your throwing range. Your thrown strikes ignore concealment and reduce the target's circumstance bonus to AC by 1.</content>
  <content contentuid="h885f2f6fg1b31g7ea8g1d5cge175754bfae5" version="1">Homebrewer</content>
  <content contentuid="h42e96563g3bddg8834g4247g72c631d2bd3d" version="1">Your hands have a genius mind of their own, measuring ratios before your memory catches up. You don't need to know its formula to create a consumable of your level or below with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_QuickAlchemy"&gt;Quick Alchemy&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4bbcef9egf369geb2age3efga618d48a2e4e" version="1">Shaped Contaminant</content>
  <content contentuid="hc965f8c5g74c2g055cg5266gdaaf6fdfbb5d" version="1">You can brew an inhaled poison and deploy it in a [1] line. Affected creatures take [2] every turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h13ae37b4gd6f8g42b2ga8bcg50b137642a68" version="1">Regurgitate Mutagen</content>
  <content contentuid="hcde69dccg5046g4bd1g68c5gada92d7c26ce" version="1">End the effects of an elixir to spit a stream of acid that deals [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h424e5ffeg1ebfg08a8g284age31e553b7eef" version="1">Regurgitate Mutagen</content>
  <content contentuid="h096c3452ge9d0g4ca8g6a82ga09435bc9d4d" version="1">End the effects of an elixir to spit a stream of acid that deals [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="hba2cc7f2g1614gdd23g8d44g2bd8e126313f" version="1">Efficient Alchemy</content>
  <content contentuid="h4ba06ca4g94dbg1fbag07ffgc23b4b029ed1" version="1">You gain [1] additional &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="InfusedReagent"&gt;infused reagents&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27c8fd31g5507g2227gf170g8aa7a447ee25" version="1">Advanced Efficient Alchemy</content>
  <content contentuid="hb5553504g1218gd14cg95e0ge07947e7997d" version="1">Fermenting Liquors</content>
  <content contentuid="h0128ecdcg00e7gba22g7676g52420d7f41bb" version="1">Serve your special batch of liquor, restoring [1] to a willing creature and giving you a +1 status bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Persuasion"&gt;Diplomacy&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc4a51b94g8f3eg9ee7g4ae1g6ee914eb3959" version="1">Fermenting Liquors</content>
  <content contentuid="hd971e743gdd81g5419g5e04gb8fa1fd4600a" version="1">Serve your special batch of liquor, restoring [1] to a willing creature and giving you a +1 status bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Persuasion"&gt;Diplomacy&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd9c3739fg6dd3ge7dbgb2b2g94561cbdc2cf" version="1">Made a toast. +1 status bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Persuasion"&gt;Diplomacy&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd8c2b708g8fabg3701g2530g5e14353a5370" version="1">Sour Bomb</content>
  <content contentuid="h9385f078g54ebg642fg2b41g82709a09c9a5" version="1">You can mix ingredients into an alchemical bomb to make its explosion an overpowering stench. Creates a [1] cloud that &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="STINKING_CLOUD"&gt;sickens&lt;/LSTag&gt; creatures within.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbbb93deegd978g136ag4f40gb89ad0c1177b" version="1">Sour Bomb</content>
  <content contentuid="h0a1090f5g08d9g688bg7065g764ce8b99fe1" version="1">When thrown, it creates a cloud that &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="STINKING_CLOUD"&gt;sickens&lt;/LSTag&gt; creatures within.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6b9554bfg204egc2a3g1a66gf9dd3b45e769" version="1">Enduring Alchemy</content>
  <content contentuid="hb0620296gcb33gc77egcfbag46e50b8f2070" version="1">Consumables made with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_QuickAlchemy"&gt;Quick Alchemy&lt;/LSTag&gt; remain potent until the end of your next turn, instead of losing potency at the start of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hecd2821ag0d66gd674g02ffgaee649db7b9e" version="1">Alter Admixture</content>
  <content contentuid="h44693a58ga3e4g6964g3992gb382551d9c62" version="1">Scrap an item to recover its &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="InfusedReagent"&gt;infused reagent&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1a092811ge9e7g0875g13d2gbe7a28370afd" version="1">Alter Admixture</content>
  <content contentuid="h9854fd38gd059g95fega07agdee8c2fa6343" version="1">Scrap an item to recover its &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="InfusedReagent"&gt;infused reagent&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf84bf4ddg49bdg37c2gc30cgd3ce57bc919a" version="1">Must have an infused item.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2034fcc7ga032g777eg5db1g5d29677487f7" version="1">Not yet learned.</content>
  <content contentuid="h96c4b481g128bgf4d1g8a7agf2944e7eeb89" version="1">Not high enough level to craft this item.</content>
  <content contentuid="hae7c0411g7040g9c4dg7b12g6e340b37d597" version="1">Target is too young.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7072c477g733ag45ffg6a63g2486539e3e10" version="1">Miracle Worker</content>
  <content contentuid="h6b6a907dg0384ge446g00e3g6bcff2abfb87" version="1">Administer a special concoction to revive an ally.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcde9600fg8893g339ag54a6g03f713649b2c" version="1">Miracle Worker</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd44aee3g5d65gffb1g4f6bg04314e514ec2" version="1">Already used an additive this round.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3968b15dg9669g7e34g8cb5g6fe07f5e7e95" version="1">You can only apply one additive to &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_QuickAlchemy"&gt;Quick Alchemy&lt;/LSTag&gt; per round, and only in combat.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6e6af4bag9b3age836gd807g4a397cf1dbcb" version="1">Requires &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="FarLobber"&gt;Far Lobber&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h454c2b8bgea1dg9a5eg6f9ag76a1571d1cb9" version="1">Requires &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="InvigoratingElixir"&gt;Invigorating Elixir&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9020768bgc5aeg8d72g0312g9a8ce203ee7b" version="1">In addition, you are immune to the negative effects of being &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DRUNK"&gt;Drunk&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5a9896b3g096fg6dabg4544g1aae341aa768" version="1">Fortified Elixir</content>
  <content contentuid="h6a4526c6g3b18g10efg32beg310a0057b57c" version="1">Can end this effect to reroll a Fortitude save.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd9d12f86g09e6g3483g4cbfg7f078c2eaa89" version="1">Fortified Antidote</content>
  <content contentuid="hbbe6d050g5b20geb08g2c77g6d835619dd82" version="1">Reroll a failed Fortitude save, ending the effects of your Fortified Elixir.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3aedf88agb387ga2b8g47ffge174d035824f" version="1">Fortified Elixirs</content>
  <content contentuid="hbed4eb30gbb53gf3cbgb205g2279e0aaebc6" version="1">Your antidotes are especially efficacious. A creature affected by it can reroll one failed Fortitude save, ending the item's duration.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6e1fbf0fg4c1ag16dcg5d27g21a0c64006a0" version="1">Antidote</content>
  <content contentuid="h5876632dg04ddg46a0ge110ga8a8b1560777" version="1">Remedial Potion</content>
  <content contentuid="hd02be0f9g5766g2245g9320g201addc54eb7" version="1">May remove bleeding.</content>
  <content contentuid="h01f000c7g30f4g0606g8c04gc35ea7f84522" version="1">Pharmacopoeia</content>
  <content contentuid="h343b70bfgd838g3655g904bga733b62a030e" version="1">Gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;temporary hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to the creator's &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt; modifier for 1 minute.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb049dd12g44ddg6e56gc18dg4f5dc5acef26" version="1">Field Vials: Poison Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="hdfd12956g168eg958dg8d0age1e9a6a0ce68" version="1">Invigorating Elixir</content>
  <content contentuid="h447ad9d4gb74ag2724g41ecg0fc5905b0c5d" version="1">Removes several conditions with a DC 10 flat check.</content>
  <content contentuid="hac5b28f3g791egd0a4g0ef3gabe6a0856f8c" version="2">Temporarily immune to further uses of this additive until the next &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0d5c2d95gaf84g76d2g1c34g70f29a52c3fd" version="1">Invigorating Elixir</content>
  <content contentuid="h9dbbc42ega100gf842g4d1fgc2d417f8199d" version="1">Add an aromatic salve to a healing item. It counteracts &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CLUMSY"&gt;clumsy&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ENFEEBLED"&gt;enfeebled&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="SICKENED"&gt;sickened&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="STUPEFIED"&gt;stupefied&lt;/LSTag&gt; with a DC 10 flat check. The imbiber is then temporarily immune to this additive until the next &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h46dc78acg7682g211bgf8dfged6065047db0" version="1">* Physical Invigorating Elixir *</content>
  <content contentuid="h44bcbe1dg7ab0gb889g325cg70a471e493cb" version="1">The listed conditions can be counteracted by &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="InvigoratingElixir"&gt;Invigorating Elixir&lt;/LSTag&gt;: &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PARALYZED"&gt;paralyzed&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="SLOW"&gt;slowed&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLINDED"&gt;blinded&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ASTARION_WEAK"&gt;drained&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc25a41f0geaafg78cfgd5degb621d8a8aa36" version="1">* Mental Invigorating Elixir *</content>
  <content contentuid="h5ce31201g0678gdf8bgdf23g3d170044fec2" version="1">The listed conditions can be counteracted by &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="InvigoratingElixir"&gt;Invigorating Elixir&lt;/LSTag&gt;: &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PARALYZED"&gt;paralyzed&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="SLOW"&gt;slowed&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CONFUSION"&gt;confused&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DOMINATE_PERSON"&gt;controlled&lt;/LSTag&gt;, fleeing and &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FRIGHTENED"&gt;frightened&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9dad3e6bgfc0cgf980gf1ebg5a512be4c60b" version="1">* Supreme Invigorating Elixir *</content>
  <content contentuid="he1c23bdfg98e2g6a0dg2527g8ec6de3f9191" version="1">The listed conditions can be counteracted by &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="InvigoratingElixir"&gt;Invigorating Elixir&lt;/LSTag&gt;: &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="STUNNED1"&gt;stunned&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PETRIFIED"&gt;petrified&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and all diseases.</content>
  <content contentuid="h76d24974gaee8g3444gabb0gb2ed1b74fbbe" version="1">Debilitating Bomb</content>
  <content contentuid="h87f781c0g517ag1760g5b73g86498a9d3ab8" version="2">Add a crystaline additive to a bomb to undermine a foe. Choose &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DAZZLED_APPLY"&gt;dazzled&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DEAFENED"&gt;deafened&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="OFF_BALANCED"&gt;off-guard&lt;/LSTag&gt;, or a –[1] status penalty to Speeds. If the Strike is a direct hit, the target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or take that effect for 1 turn, even if someone else throws the bomb.</content>
  <content contentuid="h34308b03g9248g99fdgb95cg33738ddf7081" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Dazzled</content>
  <content contentuid="h2bd8ac75gc70cg134cg354agbda909b43c75" version="2">Add a crystaline additive to a bomb to undermine a foe. If the Strike is a direct hit, the target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DAZZLED_APPLY"&gt;dazzled&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 1 turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb5ad958fgb7dage4f0g75a8gda3535d2d68d" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Deafened</content>
  <content contentuid="h9b468564gc7feg8233g616agb7a11bebde45" version="2">Add a crystaline additive to a bomb to undermine a foe. If the Strike is a direct hit, the target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DEAFENED"&gt;deafened&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 1 turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha1ccc90ag9acfga1d8g9533gf9286370a5c0" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Off-Guard</content>
  <content contentuid="h3afca737g30ddga7f3g1a56gf43a4c12d725" version="2">Add a crystaline additive to a bomb to undermine a foe. If the Strike is a direct hit, the target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="OFF_BALANCED"&gt;off-guard&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 1 turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2f07a63fgd7dagd506g74bfg41c3d9b69453" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Reduced Speed</content>
  <content contentuid="h2a21c130ge1c8ge575g7515g843ac938c174" version="1">Add a crystaline additive to a bomb to undermine a foe. If the Strike is a direct hit, the target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or take a –[1] status penalty to Speeds for 1 turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="he5d8619eg2622g321cga77egc41b2ac0fb72" version="1">* Greater Debilitating Bomb *</content>
  <content contentuid="he83f69aeg522dg20e4g4fc2g405c21b1eacc" version="1">You have learned enhanced techniques and alchemical secrets that allow you to expand the range of effects you can impose with your bombs. When you use &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DebilitatingBomb"&gt;Debilitating Bomb&lt;/LSTag&gt;, add the following to the list you can choose from: &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CLUMSY"&gt;clumsy 1&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ENFEEBLED"&gt;enfeebled 1&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="STUPEFIED_1"&gt;stupefied 1&lt;/LSTag&gt;, or a –[1] status penalty to Speeds.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf95528eaga508gebd6g2eebgc7b9872e1a8f" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Clumsy</content>
  <content contentuid="hd4865a22g10bfgf443g3562ge5b1810fa98c" version="1">Add a crystaline additive to a bomb to undermine a foe. If the Strike is a direct hit, the target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CLUMSY"&gt;clumsy 1&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 1 turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h68483c74ge471ge291gbabfge2c3ae39743e" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Enfeebled</content>
  <content contentuid="hee5c4870ge4a6ge27cg9b19g9a87e0065be3" version="1">Add a crystaline additive to a bomb to undermine a foe. If the Strike is a direct hit, the target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ENFEEBLED"&gt;enfeebled 1&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 1 turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h09eb5accge527g7c84gb014g567644a8e831" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Stupefied</content>
  <content contentuid="hfc861f41g1824g82f3g921bgcdf16455d6d7" version="1">Add a crystaline additive to a bomb to undermine a foe. If the Strike is a direct hit, the target must succeed at a Fortitude save against your class DC or become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="STUPEFIED_1"&gt;stupefied 1&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 1 turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h619881c5g0241gd47bg713fg9c9672397b52" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Dazzled</content>
  <content contentuid="h31355a01gcc73g85a6gde07g2ad4209cb196" version="1">If the Strike is a direct hit, the target must succeed at a Fortitude save against the creator's class DC or take the listed effect for 1 turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbdea06f8gc664g7ce6g91beg6d0f18504e68" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Deafened</content>
  <content contentuid="h2546e72dgbdabgbef8g0bb0gf4c9317457c5" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Off-Guard</content>
  <content contentuid="h7de64d95gef5fg906bgd600g0eb25eb55303" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Reduced Speed</content>
  <content contentuid="ha2e80cb4g58e2g8262gdfc3ga6db6dd0b33f" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Enfeebled 1</content>
  <content contentuid="he74f7347g6727g1ef3ga5cdgb3063a7e94a1" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Clumsy 1</content>
  <content contentuid="ha57390bfga1f3g0b7bgfee2gb2c096bb64c5" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Stupefied 1</content>
  <content contentuid="h04dc6332ge2eeg2215g51cagd686afd53a35" version="1">Debilitating Bomb: Greater Reduced Speed</content>
  <content contentuid="h27dbad27gfa3dg03a9g272eg9e1033148798" version="1">Requires &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DebilitatingBomb"&gt;Debilitating Bomb&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcb981a68g8067g3736gf53fg6930b8187137" version="1">Web Grenade</content>
  <content contentuid="h4afc2e06g8431g07e3g512ag320bdb20d83f" version="1">Potion of Greater Healing</content>
  <content contentuid="h0b50d33fgffc3g7924gc907g27067bc88128" version="1">Potion of Superior Healing</content>
  <content contentuid="h9509ffc8ged2cg3837g026eg9d0de6d61704" version="1">Potion of Supreme Healing</content>
  <content contentuid="h6ae248f6gd958ga9c7g16d8gc7728fa7f854" version="1">Potion of Angelic Reprieve</content>
  <content contentuid="hf052b84eg29bfg5679g6ebag18116991e650" version="1">Potion of Angelic Slumber</content>
  <content contentuid="h4108700dg7842g1f5egb532gc6f6c9f28ae7" version="1">Potion of Invisibility</content>
  <content contentuid="hb9f55008g3783ga5b5ga192g556b5b2555cb" version="1">Potion of Feather Fall</content>
  <content contentuid="h408cdd79g5904g1527gadb1g96995d952b6b" version="1">Potion of Glorious Vaulting</content>
  <content contentuid="h4490e2ceg02eag04fdgac77gef88da6673e1" version="1">Potion of Flying</content>
  <content contentuid="ha7cbf16dg90aeg83f5gfa6ag48f02e84c6cf" version="1">Potion of Animal Speaking</content>
  <content contentuid="h901d258ag94abgfd4cge206g0eb727e86828" version="1">Potion of Mind Reading</content>
  <content contentuid="h371a77eege43egb3eeg9639g8665fac54672" version="1">Elixir of Darkvision</content>
  <content contentuid="h3115034egbaffg8190gb613gbc4a4f9ea138" version="1">Elixir of See Invisibility</content>
  <content contentuid="h762298bfgc85dg5adag8360g8ffff1d554f3" version="1">Elixir of Arcane Cultivation</content>
  <content contentuid="h3844f646g9d7dgebccg40f6g65ded90a2cb0" version="1">Elixir of Greater Arcane Cultivation</content>
  <content contentuid="h3fecc3a2gd797g0665gb360gdf674b20b56d" version="1">Elixir of Superior Arcane Cultivation</content>
  <content contentuid="hfa379395g0091g3068g88d2g125b4f920803" version="1">Elixir of Supreme Arcane Cultivation</content>
  <content contentuid="h070c0998g6329g32a9g0a62g5e0aac88cd35" version="1">Elixir of Vigilance</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1cc72d1g7121g98bdg4aa4g5bbbbd100e8a" version="1">Elixir of Guileful Movement</content>
  <content contentuid="h53caeb2dg1720g96eagff2cg08c8af515fe1" version="1">Potion of Speed</content>
  <content contentuid="hbe3403c5g08c7g1c31g827fg6f15ff0d985a" version="1">Haste Spore Grenade</content>
  <content contentuid="hd03a7cb6g0ccagaa1fgbac0ge4e88278fd6c" version="1">Elixir of Fire Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="hf83d43b0g1cb8g1f88g261cg422ec68f8fdc" version="1">Elixir of Cold Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h2e5ab1e1g2963g4d35g6a93g3c6c6522982d" version="1">Elixir of Lightning Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h1952718dg8099g94afgaf94gdb28bbb4acf3" version="1">Elixir of Acid Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h533a7976gdc76g7c25g0a85g4733a560a18d" version="1">Elixir of Poison Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ca6096bg0fe9gaa82ga149g6eaa1bc55a97" version="1">Elixir of Necrotic Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h3eb78dfdgb40cg5c67gacffgab3fb914c7c2" version="1">Elixir of Psychic Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h66dd7fd5g6993g239agc39agdcb8070738ee" version="1">Elixir of Universal Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h19c378f6g35fdg6310g96c2g724b579dfa08" version="1">Elixir of Barkskin</content>
  <content contentuid="h144210ebg586bgf5f6gb385g26fc3cf79a6e" version="1">Elixir of Peerless Focus</content>
  <content contentuid="h83d10ae3gcd08g9942g3a3ag6ac1512cbb44" version="1">Elixir of Battlemage's Power</content>
  <content contentuid="h601b0535gf188g1d16g7fa0g126ede3ea60c" version="1">Wizardsbane Oil</content>
  <content contentuid="he03576c1g429fg5c2eg58c6gf5737544521a" version="1">Fungal Bamboozler</content>
  <content contentuid="h9748e4fcgbe4cg70a6g9c27g9474db92f004" version="1">Tadpole Elixir</content>
  <content contentuid="ha676a00eg0aa1g3255gb7e4g67c341442e3a" version="1">Elixir of The Colossus </content>
  <content contentuid="h18135833g5bb4gaf9bg5b2fg708c3d787cfd" version="1">Your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intelligence"&gt;Intelligence&lt;/LSTag&gt; modifier determines how many infused reagents you have, which are used to make daily items with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_QuickAlchemy"&gt;Quick Alchemy&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Items crafted outside of combat will last until the next &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;long rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hce572b93g014cg7214gb0fcgce0dce38f201" version="3">Versatile vials are used to make short-lived items with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_QuickAlchemy"&gt;Quick Alchemy&lt;/LSTag&gt; in combat. Items crafted this way last until the end of your turn. In higher difficulty modes, you can only use versatile vials in combat instead of infused reagents.&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE: &lt;/b&gt; Because alchemy makes a much different set of items than in PF2, you do not add your intelligence modifier to the number of vials you recieve. At level 9 you recieve a third vial.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbf923843gaba6g9036g9e9bg165c004988b5" version="1">Flammable Slime Bomb</content>
  <content contentuid="hc5e15c4cgaa8dg556dg1cafg7b8e64e9cea0" version="1">Noxious Spore Grenade</content>
  <content contentuid="h282d8e0bg8b47gf74fgaa8ag2424dfb88885" version="1">Elixir of Heroism</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c0a05b9gbb19g6634ga829ga3716aaf486b" version="1">Elixir of Bloodlust</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ed7b43fgb19fg8fb1g4748g76b0a7821ad1" version="1">Hearthlight Bomb</content>
  <content contentuid="h72ecbb0age701ge46dgfbacg4dead71b2236" version="1">Flashblinder</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e832e81g0641gfceag4fd2g58324b86f0f2" version="1">Elixir of Viciousness</content>
  <content contentuid="hb8796a03g94dcg3dd2g56d1g2ec60c115096" version="1">Diluted Oil of Sharpness</content>
  <content contentuid="he0ff5f18ga8f7g10b5g1b8fgcb61369a92e3" version="1">Oil of Accuracy</content>
  <content contentuid="hd0fba3e5ge512g0e16gf62cg0198612f153f" version="1">Oil of Diminution</content>
  <content contentuid="h4115d30cg0658g4422g5cd8g054d5ff5ce7d" version="1">Oil of Bane</content>
  <content contentuid="h3138fbe4g531eg5dd5g1b97g7665576a6d7a" version="1">Arsonist's Oil</content>
  <content contentuid="h4103e506gf8c1g11edg7f0ag3f1a57e6d86a" version="1">Oil of Combustion</content>
  <content contentuid="h6b400745g239agd982gca4eg550c78f58950" version="1">Oil of Freezing</content>
  <content contentuid="h00c06552g5806g50a0g213egbf2f0cb5399e" version="1">Basic Poison</content>
  <content contentuid="h5e4f3326g8e87gd91ag847bge4ab602309b7" version="1">Drow Poison</content>
  <content contentuid="h81790eb5g4baagc545g4579ga2b112a07821" version="1">Crawler Mucus</content>
  <content contentuid="hc305f18ag31a2g14b8g3ac2g4c43a001f4d3" version="1">Malice</content>
  <content contentuid="h894e465cg2053g3441ge8b5g3ebe5650f919" version="1">Brewed-Up Bellyglummer</content>
  <content contentuid="h1522d264g1e65g2e2dge1e1g47594a238207" version="1">Simple Toxin</content>
  <content contentuid="h25ae4fd1g18e2gbd8cgcd31g940a3ae1c288" version="1">Serpent Fang Toxin</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d7a6686g0bd9g1d65g6f0bg64bf247c7dbf" version="1">Wyvern Toxin</content>
  <content contentuid="hc08168f3gcae1g3db8g6f1ag94e3c899cbb1" version="1">Purple Worm Toxin</content>
  <content contentuid="hb092366bg816dgabe2gcf70gf966fe1b7766" version="1">Implements Interruption</content>
  <content contentuid="hce7518fag3231gd899ga843ge82953a521e3" version="1">Implements Interruption - Concentrate, Manipulate</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1e9bf6bgc500gbdc4g24c4g305f63de1d04" version="1">Attack a creature trying to use a manipulate or cocentratge action, potentially disrupting that action.</content>
</contentList>